This CV has been designed with **you** in mind. I have seen the amount of applications an employer has to review for a single job application. Thus I have made this short and to the point. What is the purpose of an interview if I provide all info here? What would it say about me if I **can** be confined to paper?

So let me assure you that there is a lot more depth to me than the scribe on this 150micron page. Please keep this in mind when reviewing my application.

I thank you for your time and appreciate the consideration.

Kindest Regards Jacques le Roux

A GLIMPSE OF WHO I AM

I am the type of person that will research any job or task to find the most effective way of doing said job/task. I have a keen interest in neuro-linguistic programming and will therefore mull over each part that makes up the whole.

My favourite quote comes from Abraham Lincoln: "Give me 6 hours to chop down a tree and I'll spend the first 5 sharpening the blade".

I value growth and welcome challenges. I perceive them as an opportunity to learn. I take ownership of my work and will do more than what is expected of me. I am ambitious and will fight mediocrity at ever chance.

PERSONAL SIDE OF ME

I use the British spelling for words. colour, organise, dependant... etc. I am afraid of spiders and wild birds. Former baby.

Father to 2 beautiful kids.

Cayla (born 11 Jan 2008) & Cayleb (born 23 Dec 2019). My fiancée is the best mother on earth and my family will always come first.

*Favourite Song: The Woods - Majozi ft. Tresor *Favourite Book: You Are A Badass - Jen Sincero

*Favourite Movie: Anonymous

SALES & IT PROFESSIONAL

JACQUES LE ROUX

WORK HISTORY

Feb 2013 - Aug 2016

SHOPRITE GROUP OF COMPANIES

Field Services Engineer

At Shoprite I was based in the Divisional Office for the Free State and Northern Cape. As part of a team of 3, we were collectively responsible for the seamless operation of over 250 stores, including Lesotho and Botswana. It was a challenging career with numerous hours on the roads and overtime was default. Responsible for the seamless operation of IT infrastructure.

Systems included: POS Systems, Wireless & Networking Systems, Office and back Office PC Systems, Network Scales, UPS Systems etc.

Oct 2016 - Mar 2018

MASTER MATHS

User Support

Working from the head office of Master Maths I mostly did remote support for the end users. Our systems were flawless and rarely had to go out on site to resolve issues. Regular and daily maintenance on company PCs ensured the absolute minimum downtime for all employees.

Feb 2019 - Dec 2019

HOUSE AND HOME

Sales Professional

I quickly excelled as a salesperson and ranked amongst the top sales people of the company. I established customer needs and acted upon satisfying customer's desires. I drove sales to ensure monthly targets were met and exceeded as well as build customer relations to maintain a solid, loyal customer base. Follow up calls and going the extra mile, ensured that customers kept returning.

REFERENCES

MADIE CLOETE

House & Home - Branch Manager 051 502 1660 || 082 212 6021 043157@shoprite.co.za

COENIE VAN JAARSVELD

Wimpy - Franchise Owner 051 522 1446 || 082 336 6901

EDUCATION

2007 CVO SCHOOL, DANKBAAR

National Senior Certificate

2008-2011 UNIVERSITY OF THE FREE SATE

BA. General (incomplete)

2017 CAREERFOUNDRY

Web Developer Certificate

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES











GIMP

SALES & IT PROFESSIONA

JACQUES LE ROUX

PROFILE

Date of Birth 14 Feb 1989
Nationality South African
ID Number 890214 5101 08 4
Dependants 2

Marital Status Engaged
Driver's License Code B

Languages Afrikaans & English

CONTACT

Website:

jacquesleroux.herokuapp.com

Cellphone: 076 5321 085

Email:

jacques.leroux3@gmail.com

Address:

31 Saratoga Complex, Olienhout Str, Wilgehof, Bfn, 9301.

ROR

JQUERY

BOOTSTRAP

GITHUB